<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>im.dino.Dino</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">im.dino.Dino.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Dino</name>
  <summary>Modern XMPP Chat Client</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">現代化的 XMPP 聊天用戶端</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">现代 XMPP 聊天客户端</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Modern XMPP Sohbet İstemcisi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Modern XMPP-chattklient</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Современный чат-клиент на XMPP</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Client XMPP de discuții modern</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Moderno cliente de chat XMPP</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Nowoczesny komunikator XMPP</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="oc">Client XMPP modèrn</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl_BE">Modernen XMPP-chatcliënt</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Moderne XMPP-chatcliënt</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Moderne XMPP-sludreklient</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Šiuolaikinė XMPP pokalbių kliento programa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lb">Modernen XMPP Chat Client</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">現代的な XMPP チャット クライアント</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Client di chat moderno per XMPP</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ie">Un modern client de conversationes XMPP</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Modern XMPP Üzenetküldő</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Cliente moderno para conversas XMPP</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Client XMPP moderne</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">XMPP txat bezero modernoa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Cliente de XMPP moderno</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Modernes XMPP-Chat-Programm</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Client de xat XMPP modern</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">تطبيق حديث للدردشة عبر XMPP</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Dino is a modern open-source chat client for the desktop. It focuses on providing a clean and reliable Jabber/XMPP experience while having your privacy in mind.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">Dino 是一個爲桌面打造的現代化開放原始碼聊天用戶端。它致力於提供一份簡洁而可靠的 Jabber/XMPP 體驗，同時亦尊重您的隱私。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">Dino 是一个现代的开源聊天桌面客户端。它致力于提供一个清爽又可靠的 Jabber/XMPP 体验，同时又保护您的隐私。</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Dino masaüstü bilgisayarlar için modern, açık-kaynak sohbet etme uygulamasıdır. Dino kendisini Jabber/XMPP deneyimini güvenilir ve sade olarak gizlilik hassasiyetinizi dikkate alacak şekilde sunmaya odaklanmıştır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Dino är en moden chattklient för skrivbordet med öppen källkod. Den erbjuder en elegant och pålitligt upplevelse av Jabber/XMPP samtidigt som den ser efter din integritet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Dino - это современный клиент для чатов с открытым исходным кодом, направленный на  надёжное и приватное использование Jabber/XMPP на персональных компьютерах.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Dino este un client de chat modern, cu sursă deschisă, pentru calculatoare. Se concentrează să furnizeze o experiență Jabber/XMPP clară și fiabilă, ținând cont de confidențialitatea dumneavoastră.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Dino é um moderno chat de código aberto para desktop. Ele é focado em prover uma transparente e confiável experiência Jabber/XMPP, tendo em mente a sua privacidade.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Dino jest nowoczesnym, otwartym komunikatorem. Skupia się na prostej obsłudze sieci Jabber/XMPP dbając o twoją prywatność.</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Dino es un client de chat liure e modèrn per l’ordenador de burèu. Ensaja de provesir una experiéncia neta e fisabla de Jabber/XMPP en téner en compte vòstra confidencialitat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl_BE">Dino is een moderne, vrije chattoepassing voor uw bureaublad. Ze biedt een eenvoudige en betrouwbare Jabber/XMPP-ervaring, met uw privacy in het achterhoofd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Dino is een moderne, vrije chattoepassing voor uw bureaublad. Ze biedt een eenvoudige en betrouwbare Jabber/XMPP-ervaring, met uw privacy in het achterhoofd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Dino er en moderne friporg-sludringsklient for skrivebordet. Det fokuserer på rask og pålitelig XMPP-opplevelse, samtidig som det hegner om personvernet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Dino yra šiuolaikinė atvirojo kodo kliento programa skirta darbalaukiui. Jos pagrindinis dėmesys yra pateikti tvarkingą ir patikimą Jabber/XMPP patyrimą nepamirštant apie jūsų privatumą.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lb">Dino ass e modernen, quell-offene Chat Client fir den Desktop. Hien biet eng opgeraumt a robust Jabber/XMPP Erfarung a leet ee Schwéierpunkt op Privatsphär.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">Dino はオープンソースの現代的なデスクトップ向けチャットクライアントです。プライバシーを考慮しつつ、シンプルで信頼できる Jabber/XMPP エクスペリエンスの提供を第一に考えて開発されています。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Dino è un client di chat per il desktop, moderno e open-source. Si concentra nel fornire un'esperienza Jabber/XMPP pulita e affidabile tenendo presente la tua privacy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ie">Dino es un modern cliente de conversationes con fonte apert. It foca se sur provider un nett e fidibil experientie de Jabber/XMPP con un attention a confidentialitá.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Dino egy modern, nyílt forráskódú üzenetküldő alkalmazás asztali rendszerekre, ami a hangsúlyt a letisztult és megbízható Jabber/XMPP élményre helyezi, miközben a magánszféra megőrzését is fontosnak tartja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Dino é un cliente moderno e de código aberto para o escritorio. Orientado a fornecer unha experiencia Jabber/XMPP limpa e fiábel tendo a privacidade e seguranza presentes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Dino est un client de chat libre et moderne pour le bureau. Il tente de fournir une expérience Jabber/XMPP simple et fiable tout en ayant toujours à l’esprit votre vie privée.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Dino on nykyaikainen avoimen lähdekoodin jutteluohjelma työpöydälle. Se keskittyy tarjoamaan selkeän ja luotettavan Jabber/XMPP-kokemuksen unohtamatta yksityisyyttäsi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Dino mahaigainerako iturburu irekiko txat bezero moderno bat da. Jabber/XMPP esperientzia garbi eta fidagarri bat ematen du zure pribatutasuna kontuan hartzeaz gain.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Dino es un cliente de mensajería moderno y libre para escritorio. Está enfocado en proveer una experiencia Jabber/XMPP limpia y confiable teniendo tu privacidad en mente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Dino ist ein modernes, quelloffenes Chat-Programm für den Desktop. Es bietet ein aufgeräumtes und robustes Jabber-/XMPP-Erlebnis und legt einen Schwerpunkt auf Privatsphäre.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Dino és un client de xat lliure i modern per a l'escriptori. Està centrat en proveir una experiència neta i fiable de Jabber/XMPP, sempre tenint en compte la vostra privacitat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">إنّ Dino برنامج عصري ومفتوح المصدر للدردشة صُمّم لسطح المكتب. ويُركّز علي تقديم تجربة نظيفة وموثوق منها لجابر/XMPP مع أخذ خصوصيتكم بعين الإعتبار.</p>
    <p>It supports end-to-end encryption with OMEMO and OpenPGP and allows configuring privacy-related features such as read receipts and typing notifications.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">它支持 OMEMO 和 OpenPGP 兩種端對端加密方式，並且容許設定隱私相關的特性譬如已讀回條和正在輸入提示。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">它支持 OMEMO 和 OpenPGP 端对端加密并允许配置隐私相关的特性比如已读回执和输入提醒。</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">OMEMO ve OpenPGP ile baştan sona şifreleme destekler ve "okundu" bilgisi, "yazıyor..." bildirimi gibi gizlilikle alakalı özelliklerin ayarlanabilmesini sağlar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Dino stödjer end-to-end-kryptering med OMEMO och OpenPGP och tillåter konfigurering av funktioner med integritetspåverkan som läsbekräftelser och skriftaviseringar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Он поддерживает сквозное шифрование через OMEMO и OpenPGP и позволяет настраивать такие функции, как уведомления о прочтении и наборе сообщений.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Suportă criptare de la un capăt la altul prin intermediul OMEMO și OpenPGP, și permite configurarea caracteristicilor legate de confidențialitate precum trimiterea notificărilor de primire și tastare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Suporte criptografia ponta a ponta com OMEMO e OpenPGP e permite configurar privacidade—características relacionadas às notificações de leitura, recebimento e escrita.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Obsługuje szyfrowanie od końca do końca za pomocą OMEMO i OpenPGP, a także daje kontrolę nad funkcjami wpływającymi na prywatność, jak powiadomienia o pisaniu czy odczytaniu wiadomości.</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Compatible amb lo chiframent OMEMO e OpenPGP del cap a la fin e permet de configurar de foncionalitats ligadas amb la confidencialitat  coma los acusats de lectura e las notificacions d’escritura.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl_BE">Ze ondersteunt eind-tot-eind-versleuteling met OMEMO en OpenPGP, en laat u toe privacygerelateerde functies, gelijk leesbevestigingen en typmeldingen, in te stellen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Ze ondersteunt eind-tot-eind-versleuteling met OMEMO en OpenPGP, en staat u toe privacy-gerelateerde functies, zoals leesbevestigingen en typmeldingen, in te stellen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Det støtter ende-til-ende -kryptering med OMEMO og OpenPGP, og tillater oppsett av personvernsrelaterte funksjoner som meldingskvitteringer og skrivevarsling.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Ji palaiko ištisinį šifravimą naudojant OMEMO ir OpenPGP bei leidžia konfigūruoti su privatumu susijusias ypatybes, tokias kaip pranešimus apie žinučių skaitymą ir rašymą.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lb">Hien ënnerstëtz Enn-zu-Enn Verschlësselung mat OMEMO an OpenPGP an enthält Privatsphäre-Astellungen zu Liesbestätegungen an Tipp-Benoriichtegungen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">OMEMO と OpenPGP を利用したエンドツーエンド暗号化に対応しており、既読状態の送信や入力通知などのプライバシー関連の設定も可能です。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Support la crittografia end-to-end tramite OMEMO e OpenPGP e permette di configurare le funzioni relative alla privacy come le ricevute di lettura e le notifiche di digitazione.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ie">It supporta ciffration terminal per OMEMO e OpenPGP e permisse configurar sensitiv functiones quam confirmation de lectada e notificationes de tippada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Támogatja a végponttól-végpontig titkosítást az OMEMO és az OpenPGP által, és magánszférához kötődő beállítási lehetőségeket is biztosít, mint például a kézbesítési, vagy gépelési értesítések küldése.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Suporta o cifrado de punto-a-punto con OMEMO e OpenPGP e permite configurar trazos orientados á privacidade tales coma confirmación de lectura e notificacións de escritura.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Il prend en charge le chiffrement de bout en bout avec OMEMO et OpenPGP et permet de configurer les fonctions liées à la vie privée telles que l’accusé de réception et les notifications de frappe.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Se tukee päästä päähän -salausta OMEMO:n ja OpenPGP:n avulla ja  mahdollistaa yksityisyyteen liittyvien ominaisuuksien, kuten lukukuittausten ja kirjoitusilmoitusten asetusten määrittämisen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Amaieratik amaierarako enkriptazioa onartzen du OMEMO eta OpenPGPrekin eta pribatutasun ezaugarriak konfiguratzea baimentzen du irakurtze markak eta idazketa jakinarazpenak bezala.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Soporta cifrado de extremo a extremo a través de OMEMO y OpenPGP y permite configurar las características relacionadas con la privacidad, como confirmaciones de lectura y notificaciones de escritura.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Er unterstützt Ende-zu-Ende Verschlüsselung mit OMEMO und OpenPGP und enthält Privatsphäre-Einstellungen zu Lesebestätigungen und Tippbenachrichtigungen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Implementa xifratge punt a punt amb OMEMO i OpenPGP, i permet configurar funcionalitats relacionades amb la privacitat com per exemple rebuts de lectura i notificacions d'escriptura.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">وهو يدعم التشفير بواسطة OMEMO و OpenPGP يسمح بإعداد ميزات الخصوصية كالإيصالات المقروءة والإخطارات عند الكتابة.</p>
    <p>Dino fetches history from the server and synchronizes messages with other devices.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">Dino 從伺服器取得訊息並與其他裝置同步。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">Dino 从服务器获取消息并和其他设备同步。</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Dino sunucudan konuşma geçmişini sunucudan çeker ve diğer cihazlara senkronize eder.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Dino hämtar historik från servern och synkroniserar meddelanden med andra enheter.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Dino загружает историю с сервера и синхронизирует сообщения с другими устройствами.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Dino preia istoricul discuțiilor de pe server și sincronizează mesajele cu celelalte dispozitive.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Dino obtém o histórico do servidor e sincroniza mensagens com outros dispositivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Dino pobiera historię rozmów z serwera i synchronizuje wiadomości z innymi urządzeniami.</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Dino recupèra l’istoric del servidor e sincroniza los messatges amb d’autres periferics.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl_BE">Dino haalt de geschiedenis op van de server en synchroniseert berichten met andere apparaten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Dino haalt de geschiedenis op van de server en synchroniseert berichten met andere apparaten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Dino henter historikk fra tjeneren og synkroniserer meldinger med andre enheter.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Dino gauna istoriją iš serverio ir sinchronizuoja žinutes su kitais įrenginiais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lb">Dino rifft  Gespréichverläf vum Server of a synchroniséiert Noriichte mat anere Geräter.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">Dino はサーバーから履歴を取得し、ほかのデバイスとメッセージを同期します。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Dino recupera la cronologia dal server e sincronizza i messaggi con gli altri dispositivi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ie">Dino obtene li diarium del servitore e sincronisa missages inter altri apparates.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Dino lekéri a chat előzményeket a szerverről, és szinkronizálja az üzeneteket a többi eszközzel.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Dino obtén o histórico dende o servidor e sincroniza as mensaxes con outros dispositivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Dino récupère l’historique du serveur et synchronise les messages avec d'autres appareils.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Dino hakee historian palvelimelta ja synkronisoi viestit muiden laitteiden kanssa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Dinok zerbitzaritik hartzen du historia eta beste gailuekin mezuak sinkronizatzen ditu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Dino recupera los mensajes desde el servidor y sincroniza los mensajes con otros dispositivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Dino ruft Gesprächsverläufe vom Server ab und synchronisiert Nachrichten mit anderen Geräten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Dino recupera l'historial del servidor i sincronitza els missatges amb altres dispositius.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يقوم Dino بجلب السِجلّ مِن السيرفر ثم يُزامِن الرسائل مع الأجهزة الأخرى.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Main window with conversations</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">含有對話的主視窗</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">带有对话的主窗口</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Huvudfönster med konversationer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Главное окно с чатами</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Fereastra principală de conversații</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_BR">Janela principal com as conversas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Główne okno rozmów</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="oc">Fenèstra màger amb conversacions</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl_BE">Hoofdvenster met gesprekken</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Hoofdvenster met gesprekken</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Hovedvindu med samtaler</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Pagrindinis langas su pokalbiais</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lb">Haaptfënster mat den Conversatiounen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">トーク中のメインウィンドウ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">La finestra principale con le conversazioni</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ie">Li primari fenestre con conversationes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">A fő ablak a beszélgetésekkel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Lapela principal con conversas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Fenêtre principale avec des conversations</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Keskustelut pääikkunassa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Leiho nagusia elkarrizketekin</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Ventana principal con conversaciones</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Hauptfenster mit Konversationen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Finestra principal amb converses</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">النافذة الرئيسية بالمُحادثات</caption>
      <image height="900" width="1600">https://dino.im/img/appdata/main.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Start Conversation</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">開始對話</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">开始聊天</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Sohbete Başla</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Starta Chatt</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Начать чат</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Pornește o conversație</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_BR">Iniciar conversa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Rozpocznij rozmowę</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="oc">Començar la discussion</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl_BE">Gesprek beginnen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Gesprek beginnen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Start samtale</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Pradėti pokalbį</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lb">Konversatioun starten</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">トークを開始</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Inizia una conversazione</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ie">Iniciar un conversation</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Csevegés kezdeményezése</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Comezar conversa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Commencer une discussion</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Aloita keskustelu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fa">شروع گفتگو</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Elkarrizketa hasi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Iniciar Conversación</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Komenci Konversacion</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Unterhaltung starten</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Inicia una conversa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">الشروع في محادثة</caption>
      <image height="900" width="1600">https://dino.im/img/appdata/start_chat.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Contact Details</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">聯絡人詳細資訊</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">联系人详情</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Kişi Detayları</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Kontaktdetaljer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Информация о контакте</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Detalii contact</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_BR">Detalhes do contato</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Szczegóły kontaktu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="oc">Detalhs del contacte</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl_BE">Contactgegevens</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Contactgegevens</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Kontaktdetaljer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Išsamiau apie adresatą</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lb">Kontaktdetailer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">連絡先の詳細</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Dettagli del contatto</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ie">Detallies del contacte</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Felhasználó információ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Detalles do contacto</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Informations du contact</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Yhteystiedot</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Kontaktuaren xehetasunak</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Detalles del contacto</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Kontaktaj Detaloj</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Kontaktdetails</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Detalls del contacte</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">تفاصيل عن المُراسل</caption>
      <image height="900" width="1600">https://dino.im/img/appdata/contact_details.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <translation type="gettext">dino</translation>
  <developer_name>Dino Development Team</developer_name>
  <url type="homepage">https://dino.im</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/dino/dino/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://liberapay.com/Dino</url>
  <url type="translate">https://hosted.weblate.org/projects/dino/</url>
  <!-- TODO: Point this to a webpage with documentation when there is one
  <url type="help">http://dino.im/help/</url>
  -->
  <update_contact>appstream@dino.im</update_contact>
  <!-- TODO: Write this when Dino is released
  <releases>
    <release date="XXXX-XX-XX" version="X.X">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is our first release. It comes with a clean UI, notifications,
          end-to-end encryption support (OMEMO and GnuPG), multi-user chats,
          and more!
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  -->
</component>
